http://www.computereng.com/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICYCEI TAKES YOUR PRIVACY SERIOUSLYPrivacy PolicyWe are people, customers, friends, and family members. We respect your privacy just the same as we expect others to respect ours.We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.We don’t store personal information unless absolutely necessary.Please read below and if you wish to delete or correct your personal data, please see below or contact our support team.Like most website operators, CEI collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. CEI’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how CEI’s visitors use its website.CEI also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments in the website. CEI only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the page where the comment was left.Certain visitors to CEI’s websites choose to interact with CEI in ways that require CEI to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that CEI gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who send us feedback or a support request supply an email address and company name. Those who engage in transactions with CEI – by purchasing software subscriptions, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, CEI collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with CEI. CEI does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.CEI may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, CEI may monitor the most popular pages on the site. However, CEI does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.CEI discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on CEI’s behalf or to provide services available at CEI’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using CEI’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. CEI will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, CEI discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when CEI believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of CEI, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a CEI website and have supplied your email address, CEI may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with CEI and our products. We primarily use our blog and RSS feed to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. CEI takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. CEI uses cookies to help CEI identify and track visitors, their usage of CEI website, and their website access preferences. CEI visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using CEI’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of CEI’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.If CEI, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that CEI goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of CEI may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.Although most changes are likely to be minor, CEI may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in CEI’s sole discretion. CEI encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (816) 228-2976 or via email at info@thinkcei.com.CEI’s mission is to provide innovative tools to enable our clients to excel in the welding and pressure vessel industries. Quick LinksHomeDesignCalcsFinglowProWriteDesign SolutionsWelding SolutionsApplicationsAboutThink TankBlogsWebinarsPublicationsExisting CustomersCustomer Downloads & SupportContact
816-228-2976
Send Us A Message
801 NW St. Mary Drive, Suite 205 Blue Springs, MO 64014-2539 Scroll to top
English
Portuguese
English
